{"data":[{"question":"A table made of wood is a ______.","a":"wood table","b":"table wood","c":"wood's table","d":"wooden table","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun \n+ Structure: Adj + Noun \n+ wood (n) - wooden (adj) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I've written a story about love.' 'Oh, yes. You've written a ______'","a":"love story","b":"story love","c":"story's love","d":"love's story","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They are collecting money for ______.","a":"needy","b":"the needy","c":"needing","d":"the needy poeple","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The needy(n): poor people","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The 'windows of the dining room' may be expressed as the dining ______.","a":"room's windows","b":"windows' room","c":"room windows","d":"windows room","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She had beautiful ______.","a":"golden hair","b":"gold hair","c":"golden's hair","d":"gold's hair","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun \n+ Structure: Adj + Noun \n+ Gold (n) - golden (adj)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"This money is for ______ of the parish.","a":"the people poor","b":"poor","c":"the poor","d":"poor people","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+\"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"As a rule, the ______ are very intelligent.","a":"Japanese","b":"Japanese people","c":"people Japanese","d":"Japanesemen","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjectives are often used as nouns to play role as a subject, object, or complement in a sentence. In this case, noun is often hidden \n+\"The\" is combined with these adjectives so that they can be used as nouns. \n+These adjectives are always plural and take a plural verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We had better open the ______.","a":"kitchen window","b":"window kitchen","c":"window's kitchen","d":"kitchen's window","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I was caught in a ______ on my way to the office.","a":"traffic jam","b":"jam traffic","c":"jam's traffic","d":"traffic's jam","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I could hear the ______ ringing.","a":"door bell","b":"bell door","c":"bell's door","d":"door's bell","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}